{
    "question": "Apa saja sifat-sifat hewan dalam bahasa inggris ?",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "setia = Faithful<br>Liar= wild<br>Galak=Fierce<br>Patuh=Obedient<br>Pemalas=idler<br>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "deskripsi-tumbuhan-dengan-bahasa-inggris-265",
            "question": "Deskripsi tumbuhan dengan bahasa inggris",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>\nPLANTS</span>\n<br><span>\nPlants are living beings. They need food,\nwater, and air for survival. Plants derive their food from the earth and the\nair. If you at their roots, you will find that\u2019s the ends of these roots are\nlike fine fibers. We call them root hairs. They absorb water and minerals, then\ntransport them upwards to the leaves through the trunk and the branches. It is\nthe leaves which prepare the food.</span>\n\n<span>The green material, chlorophyll present in the\nleaves prepare the food like a machine. It converts the carbon dioxide from the\nair and water from the ground into sugar with the help of sunlight. This\nchemical reaction is called photosynthesis. In fact, the chlorophyll takes\nenergy from the sunlight and uses it to synthesize the hydrogen from water and\ncarbon from carbon dioxide for making sugar. This reaction also gives out\noxygen and water which are excreted by the leaves.</span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "example of description of plants is cactus.<br><br>\n\nDescription of cactus\n\nCactus is one of\nplants who has a unique characteristic. Cactus is a plant have a thorn, the\nthorn of cactus is individualty from cactus it\u2019s causes there are many people\nlike cactus, cactus have a green colour, cactus have a round shape, other\ncharacteristic of cactus is cactus needn\u2019t flush everyday, cactus just need a\nsunlight to living on. Unique Shape of cactus is reason of people like cactus.\n\nThat\u2019s all about my\ndescription about cactus. \n\n<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "bisa-bantu-gak-verb-2-dari-write-buy-830",
            "question": "Bisa bantu gak?\r\nverb 2 dari:\r\nwrite, buy",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "write = wrote\u00a0<br>buy = bought",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Kalo write itu wrote, kalo buy itu bought",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buatlah-teks-deskripsi-bahasa-inggris-tentang-ular-320",
            "question": "Buatlah teks deskripsi bahasa inggris tentang ular\u00a0",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>The snake is one of the most successful reptiles thrive in the world . In mountains , forests , deserts , plains , farms , neighborhoods , to the sea , may be found snakes . <span>However, as is generally cold-blooded animals , snakes increasingly \nrare in cold places , such as on the tops of the mountains , in the area\n of \u200b\u200bIreland and New Zealand and the regional areas of snow or polar \ndesert .<br><br></span>Many kinds of snakes all his life wandering in the trees and almost never hit the ground . Many other types of life creeping over the surface of the soil or infiltrate infiltrate under litter or piles of rocks . <span>While most of the other living aquatic or semi - aquatic in rivers , swamps , lakes , and seas .<br><br></span>Snakes prey on various species of animals smaller than her body . Aquatic snakes prey on fish , frogs , tadpoles , fish and even eggs . Snakes and tree snakes prey on terrestrial birds , mammals , frogs , reptiles kinds of others, including its eggs . <span>Large snakes such as pythons and development can prey goats, deer , elk and even humans </span></span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-dialog-meminta-memberi-fakta-dalam-bahasa-inggris-106",
            "question": "Contoh dialog meminta, memberi fakta dalam bahasa inggris?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Dialog meminta bantuan:<br>Zevana\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 : What are you cooking, Mom?<br>Mrs. Anne : I&#039;m making vegetable soup<br>Zevana\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 : It must be yummy<br>Mrs. Anne : Surely. Hmm, would you please help me, dear?<br>Zevana\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 : Certainly, Mom. How can I help you?<br>Mrs. Anne : Please cut the potatoes and carrots<br>Zevana\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 : Right away, Mom.<br><br>Dialog memberi fakta:<br>Rio : Yesterday I met a girl at a pharmacy. We introduced ourselves and had a chitchat. Her name is Mona.<br>Feby : Mona? She might be my classmate.<br>Rio : She said so. She wears spectacles, right?<br>Feby : Yes, she is tall and has curly hair. Um.. wait a minute. I have a photograph of her. Her it is.<br>Rio : Let me see.. Well, yes, this is the girl I met yesterday. Anyway, may I have her phone number? I forgot to ask her for it.<br>Feby : Sorry, I can&#039;t give it to you now. I&#039;ll ask Mona&#039;s permission first.<br>Rio : O.K<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "siapa-yg-menciptakan-baju-pertama-kali-981",
            "question": "Siapa yg menciptakan baju pertama kali",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "nabi adam. pas waktu di usir ke bumi. beliau dan kekasihnya memakai baju dari daun2nan ...",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "dulu pertama kali adalah nabi adam<br>tapi sejarah\u00a0<span>Caerleon dari inggris yang membuat<br><br>Menurut saya sih Penjahit</span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "timowhy-didnt-didi-want-to-go-home-gerardhis-mother-him-f-879",
            "question": "timo:Why didn't Didi want to go home? gerard:his mother ... him for causing the car accident. \u00a0 a.would blame b.blames c.had blamed d.blamed",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Jawaban :\u00a0<strong><br>a. Would blame</strong>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-binggris-nya-dari-mana-saja-kamu-930",
            "question": "Apa b.inggris nya dari mana saja kamu?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "where do you come from ?",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "membuat-pidato-bahasa-inggris-tentang-menjaga-kebersihan-lingkung-502",
            "question": "Membuat pidato bahasa inggris tentang menjaga kebersihan lingkungan sekolah",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>Assalamualaikum wr wb.<br>and good afternoon<br>The Honourable mothers and fathers who are present in this place<br>\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 first of all I would like say thank to the Almighty God who has given us a good healt so we can join in this nice place.<br>\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 The second time, do not forget I said thank to the our Prophet Muhammad Saw had brought us from the realm of darkness into the lightness<br>In addition, I would like say thank to the audience for allowing me to deliver my speech with the theme of keeping the environment clean<br>well, my beloved brothers and sisters<br>\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 Keeping the environment clean is a way and the actions we can do to be able to obtain the beauty and the beauty of the environment, other than that if we always keep the environment around us, our environment will be maintained and healthy so that we can all farthest from various diseases.<br>A healthy environment would be more fun and comfortable to live in the neighborhood of a dirty\u00a0 filled with garbage strewn everywhere.<br>My beloved brothers and Sisters<br>\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 We have seen so many benefits that can be obtained if we keep the environment clean, therefore we as a society that cares about the environment, let us together to preserve the environment around us to look comfortable and cool in the view<br>and always a pleasant environment.</span><span>My beloved Brothers and Sisters<br>\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 So what can I say, if there are sentences that are less pleasing to you, I apologize, because there is no ivory that is not going to crack and there would be no human beings make mistakes.<br>thank you for your attention and wasalamualaikum wr wb.<br></span><span><br><br></span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-postcard-dalam-bahasa-inggris-untuk-teman-925",
            "question": "Contoh postcard dalam bahasa inggris untuk teman",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "hello Friend <br>How are you ?<br>i hope you are in a good condition<br>in here i very sad<br>because i miss you my friends<br>i promise to see you my friends<br>i love you my friends<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Dear, Ann<br>Hello my friend! long time no see. I miss you so much since we seperated in Junior High School. I hope your family and you&#039;re fine. Don&#039;t forget to reply me a letter, Have a nice Day!<br><br>Susan.",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-bahasa-inggrisnya-buku-berada-di-atas-meja-dan-pulpan-berada-397",
            "question": "Apa bahasa inggrisnya buku berada di atas meja dan pulpan berada di bawah meja",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "there are book on the table and the pen under the table<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "the book is on the table and the pen is under the table :) jadikan yg terbaik ya!<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}